Carl glass repair glass.
>> What later became Carglass was founded
back in [music] 1932.
Today we are a part of Belron and Belron
and Carlos are the global leader in
vehicle glass repair, [music]
replacement and recalibration. We needed
a system that could keep up with our
ambitions in terms of scalability, data
[music] access and collaboration. So we
started out upgrading our ERP onrem
solution to the cloud. Moving to the
cloud seemed like an obvious choice for
us in order to move forward and stay
relevant. We have over a hundred of
repair shops across Sweden or [music]
branches as we like to call them. And
before we move to Business Central,
coordination of [music] bookings was
quite a struggle. Today, customers have
suggested the next available time slot
for the closest branch and a technician
is automatically reserved when the
booking is placed. The information is
then instantly available in the dimeuler
overview and this [music] is a huge
improvement compared to the previous way
of working. Choosing Microsoft felt like
a natural step since we use Dynamics now
for several years now [music] and we
also use Microsoft 365 suit across the
organization. So staying within [music]
Microsoft ecosystem just made sense for
us.
>> We at Cosmo have great experiences in
bringing customers like Garlass to
cloud. But it doesn't stop there.
[music] Migrating data from onrem to
cloud solution, it's only one part.
Connecting [music] data and making it
smart, it's the actual game changer.
When moving to business center cloud, we
saw immediate improvements. The booking
site and the booking board [music] runs
much faster and we get access to data in
real time. And what really stood out is
the positive impact it had on customer
[music] satisfaction.